(Sheldon:)And good evening to you, Siam Palace.
(Sheldon:)This is Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to be dining alone
this evening...
(Sheldon:)...so I'll be reducing my usual order.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to start with one quarter
of the Assorted Appetizers Plate...
...and one half
of the Golden Treasure for two--
(Sheldon:)Oh, for heaven's sake.
In the mid-18th century...
(Sheldon:)...King Rama IV of Siam
divided a huge empire...
(Sheldon:)...amongst the colonial powers of Europe
to preserve his throne.
(Sheldon:)Surely you, his cultural descendant,
can handle pad thai and dumplings.
PENNY:
Sheldon, help!
(Sheldon:)I need to go, but you keep in mind...
(Sheldon:)...that my sharply worded comments
on Yelp.com...
(Sheldon:)...recently took down
a local muffin store.
Penny. Penny. Penny.
PENNY:
Come in! Hurry!
[SHOWER RUNNING]
(Sheldon:)-Penny?
PENNY: I'm back here.